MAREK KOBYLARCZYK

FRONT-END DEVELOPER



About me

Hello! I'm Marek Kobylarczyk, as a front-end developer I'm trying to build cool, clean & eye-pleasing websites and superb user experiences

I finished high school with a certificate of IT Specialist. I learn new technologies on my own from many websites.

Data

date of birth 24/03/97

english

Back-End:

> NodeJS

> Express

> Handlebars

> MongoDB

> SQL (basics)

> REST API

Design:

> UI/UX

> Figma

understanding

> Adobe XD

> MySQL (basics)

Key skills

Front-End:

- > HTML5
- > CSS3 (BEM)
- > SCSS, SASS
- > Javascript
- > Typescript
- > Angular
- > React (basics)
- > Gulp

Tools:

- > VSC
- > NPM
- > Git
- > Github
- > Gitlab
- Clickup
- > Trello

Experience

Front-End Developer at ISENO SP ZOO November 2020 - Present

- Creating new features, funtionality and capabilities on the eCommerce projects using Angular
- Transforming the design into a live website with cross-devices (RWD) compatibiliy
- Integrating the frontend views using JSON data from backend
- Performing bug fixes and e2e tests
- Supporting other front-end developers with code-review

Customer Advisor at Samsung Brand Store, Warsaw March 2018 - September 2020

- Customer service in the field of sales (also technical)
- Implementation of entrusted sales plans
- Cooperation with the sales / marketing department
- Taking care of Visual Merchandising
- Acting as a Samsung Brand Ambassador

Education

IT Specialist, Zespół Szkół Elektronicznych im. Bohaterów Westerplatte, Radom

September 2013 - April 2017

Projects

WeatherApp

github

My first, more extensive project based on frontend and backend, where the user can check the weather for the upcoming hours for many cities.

github TodoApp

SPA project written as part of learning the javascript language. The logic of the script is to add / remove tasks in a very simple graphic design.

Rzeczoznawca majątkowy

github

That was the first commercial project that I had to implement in a very short period time. However, full responsiveness has been maintained.

Contact

e-mail

marek.kobylarczyk@gmail.com

repository

github.com/marek9499

phone

732013413

Soft skills

- > Team Player
- > Communicative
- > Fast Learner
- > Open-Minded

Hobbies

- > Photography
- > Internet of Things
- > Bike tours
- > Cooking

"I agree to the processing of personal data provided in this document for realising the recruitment process pursuant to the Personal DataProtection Act of 10 May 2018 (Journal of Laws 2018, item 1000) and in agreement with Regulation (EU) 2016/679 of the EuropeanParliament and of the Council of 27 April 2016 on the protection of natural persons with regard to the processing of personal data and on thefree movement of such data, and repealing Directive 95/46/EC (General Data Protection Regulation)".